toptensocialmedia.com 2016-05-04

# Privacy Policy

Updated October 15, 2013

This privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to the Web site located at [http://www.toptensocialmedia.com](http://www.toptensocialmedia.com/) (the “Site”). Top Ten Social Media provides an online informative site regarding Social Media (the “Services”). This Policy is designed to tell you how we collect and use personal information (as defined below) so you can make an informed decision about using our Site and our Services. Please read this statement before using our Site or submitting any personal information to us. This Site is not intended for use by children under 13. By using our Site, you represent that you are 13 years old or older and that you consent to the information collection and use practices described herein. **We reserve the right to change the provisions of this privacy policy at any time, but we will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the privacy policy the date it was last updated. Your use of the Site following the posting of such changes or revised statement shall constitute your acceptance of any such changes.** We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you visit our Site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.

Personal information may also be collected in a number of ways when you visit our Site or use the various services and activities available on our Site. At several places on our Site, we may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, when you register for the Site or provide feedback or if you send us an email, we may collect personal information such as your name, address, phone and email and other contact information, as well as demographic and other personal information. Personal information may also be collected if you provide personal information in connection with creating a profile, leaving comments, providing reviews, participating in groups, discussions or other interactive features of the site or inviting a friend. In addition, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you provide in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities on the Site.

When you visit our Site, some information is also automatically collected through the use of log files, such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site and your activity on the Site. We use this information for purposes such as analyzing trends, administering the Sites, improving customer service, diagnosing problems with our servers, tracking user movement, and gathering broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small data files that are stored on a user’s hard drive at the request of a Web site to enable the site to recognize users who have previously visited them and retain certain information such as customer preferences and history. If we combine cookies with or link them to any of the personally identifying information, we would treat this information as personal information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn about these functions. However, if a browser is set not to accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, you will not be able to sign in and will not be able to access certain Site features or Services.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)

To send periodic emails (The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.)

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Top Ten Social Media endeavors to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure by putting into place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect through this Site. For example, your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. To protect the confidentiality of your personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately by emailing us at questions at TopTenSocialMedia.com if you believe your password has been misused. You should also note that email is not secure, and you should not send any confidential or sensitive information to us via an unsecured email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Collection of information from children under 13**

This Site is not directed to children under 13. By registering for or subscribing to the Services or by using the Site, users represent to us that they are 13 or over, and we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone we actually know is under 13 years of age.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.toptensocialmedia.com/terms-conditions/>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via the “Contact Page” on this website.
